[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "What is the the capital of Spain?",
    "answers": ["Barcelona", "Madrid", "Seville"],
    "correctIndices": [1]
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "What percentage of global land area do the forest cover?",
    "answers": ["31%", "32%", "45%", "35%"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "Which industry is known for being the largest consumers of water?",
    "answers": ["Aerospace", "Education", "Agriculture", "Chemical"],
    "correctIndices": [2]
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "Which among the following is the largest forest in the world?",
    "answers": ["Sagano Bamboo Forest", "Taiga", "Crooked Forest", "Black Forest"],
    "correctIndices": [1]
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "Which famous world leader was accused at the Rivonia Trial?",
    "answers": ["Martin Luther King", "Subhas Chandra Bose", "Nelson Mandela"],
    "correctIndices": [2]
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": " What is parasol a kind of?",
    "answers": ["Umbrella", "Footware", "Bracelet"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "The capital of which Scandinavian country is located on the islands of Zealand and Amager?",
    "answers": ["Norway", "Sweden", "Denmark"],
    "correctIndices": [2]
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "In Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea, what was the name of the warship in which Captain Nemo sailed?",
    "answers": ["Basillus", "Nautilus", "Remolus"],
    "correctIndices": [1]
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "Adams, Leverrier, Galle and Lassell are some of the rings of which planet?",
    "answers": ["Neptune", "Saturn", "Jupiter"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Which famous philosopher was also the tutor of Alexander the Great?",
    "answers": ["Aristotle", "Socrates", "Rousseau"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "The name of which of these means the ‘gilded one’ in Spanish?",
    "answers": ["El Dorade", "Buenos Aires", "El Nino"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "Which 1852 book was smuggled into Russia in Yiddish to evade the czarist censor?",
    "answers": ["Uncle Tom’s Cabin", "Alice in Wonderland", "Das Kapital"],
    "correctIndices": [0]
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "Who was the prime minister of the United Kingdom at the time of Queen Elizabeth II’s coronation?",
    "answers": [" Neville Chamberlain", "Winston Churchill", "Harold McMillan"],
    "correctIndices": [1]
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "Which of these are not a fruit",
    "answers": ["Carrot", "Orange", "Turnip", "Apple", "Parsnip"],
    "correctIndices": [0, 2, 4]
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "Which of these are part of the fibonacci sequence",
    "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5"],
    "correctIndices": [0, 1, 2, 4]
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "Which of these are not colours of the rainbow",
    "answers": ["Green", "Black", "Orange", "Red", "Yellow"],
    "correctIndices": [1, 2]
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "Which of these cities have host the olympics",
    "answers": ["Athens", "Paris", "St. Louis", "London", "Stockholm"],
    "correctIndices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "Which of these counties failed to qualify for the 2019 World Cup",
    "answers": ["Italy", "England", "Portugal", "Chile"],
    "correctIndices": [1, 3]
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "Which years did a moon landing occur",
    "answers": ["1968", "1969", "1972"],
    "correctIndices": [1, 2]
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "Which of these books were written by George Orwell",
    "answers": ["1984", "Catch 22", "Fahrenheit 451", "Animal Farm"],
    "correctIndices": [0, 3]
  }
]